Alexander, Gabriel Additional Arbitration Files 5602
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- International Harvester Company and UAW Memphis Works Case No. 348, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- International Harvester Company and UAW West Putnam Works Case No. 349, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Farmall Works Case No. 350, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 353, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 354, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 355, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 356, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 357, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 358, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 359, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 361, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 360, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 362, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 361, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 364, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 365, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 366, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 357, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 368, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 369, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 370, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 371, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 372, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 373, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 374, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 375, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 376, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 377, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 378, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 379, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- International Harvester Company and UPGWA Miller Discharge, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 380, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- International Harvester Company and UPGWA, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 381, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 382, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 383, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 384, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 385, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 387, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 388, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 389, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 390 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 391, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 392, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 393, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 394, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- International Harvester Company and UAW Case No. 395, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- McClouth Steel Corp and United Steelworkers of Amer. Gr. #67, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- McClouth Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Melling Forging Co. and UAW Local 724 Gr. #2090, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Melling Forging Co. and UAW Local 724 Case #2091, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Mich. State Univ. and Local 1585 AFSCME, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- National Broach & Machine Div. of Lear-Siegler, Inc. and USW Local 7489 Gr. No. 70-007, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- North Range Mining Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Oakland County Road Commission and Local No. 92, Council 23 AFSCME, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- In the Matter of the Reclassification of Jean Ostrander(UAW Unit of OEIU Local 42), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  November 26, 1962
- Local 42, Office Emp. Int'l Union and Int'l Union, UAW, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Ohio Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America, Local 118, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Ohio Edison Company and Local 118, Utility Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Ohio Edison and Local 126, U.W.U.A. Case # 6 Gr. # GPR 69-5 (James Crabtree), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Ohio Edison Company and Local 126, Utility Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Ohio Edison Company and Local 118, Utility Workers Union of America GPR#62-29, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Ohio Edison Company and Local 118 U.W.U.A. G.P.R.Nos. 67-10 to 67-17, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Ohio Edison Co. and Local 126 Utility Workers Union of America, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Ohio Edison Company and I.B.E.W., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Great Lakes Steel Corp. and U.P.G.W.A. Local 114 Arb. #1-65, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- The Hanna Furnace Corp. Buffalo, N.Y. and United Steelworkers of Am. Local Union 2497, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- The Hanna Furnace Corp. Buffalo, N.Y. and United Steelworkers of Am., Local Union 2497 Gr. #B-781, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- The Hanna Furnace Corp. Buffalo, N.Y. and United Steelworkers of Am., Local Union 2497, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- The Hanna Furnace Corp. Buffalo, N.Y. and United Steelworkers of Am. Local Union 2497 Gr. #B-780, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Hanna Mining Co. and United Steelworkers, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Hanna Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America Gr. #114, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Hanna Mining (Homer Gr. 266) and USW, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Hanna Company (Groveland Gr. #16), 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Hanna Mining - Hibbing, Minn. (Morton Mine-Pumpman Grievance and USWA, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- The Hanna Mining Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1624 Gr. #316, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hanna Mining Company and United Steelworkers Local 2714 Dist. 33, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Hanna Mining Co. and United Steelworkers Local 1438, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- M.A. Hanna Company (Cannon Grievance. #102) and United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Harnischfeger Corp and Steelworkers Local 1114, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Harnischfeger Corp. and USW Local 1114 Gr. #70-236, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Harnischfeger and UAW Local 632 Gr. #AC-5225, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Harnischfeger and UAW Local 632, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Harnischfeger Corp. and International Assoc. of Bridge, Structure. & Ornamental. Iron Workers - Local 814, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Harnischfeger Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Local 1114, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Hayes-Albion Corp. and UAW, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Holly Spring Company and U.A.W., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Indiana & Michigan electric and IBEW Gr. # MA 70-02, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Indiana and Mich. Electric and Local 2292, IBEW Gr. SB 70-02, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Indiana & Mich. Electric Co. Tanners Creek Generating Div. and Utility Workers Union of America - Local Union 418, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Inland Steel Co. and USW Local 5000, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Inland Steel Company and USW Gr. #35,36 Sherwood Mine, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Local No. 1357, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and USW, Local No. 3494, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel corp. and USW, Local No. 3494 Grev.# 64-15, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and USW, Local, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. Niles, Ohio, Plant Grievance #67-5 and U.S.W. of Amer.#86, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and USW, Local 3494 Gr.#65-17, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Local Union 1357 Case# 70-100, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Latrobe Steel Company and USW Gr.# 9365C, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Latrobe Steel Company and USW Grievance. Nos. 90,103, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Latrobe Steel Company and USW - Grievance Nos. 20,21,30, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Latrobe Steel Company and USW Grievance Nos. 30,47,68, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- McClouth Steel and United Steelworkers of America Case #67-1, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Lake Shore, Inc. and Local Union 3111, USW, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- McLouth Steel Corp. and USWA - Local, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- McLouth Steel Corp. and USWA, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- American Sunroof Company and United Automobile Workers Local 985 Gr. No. 6806-6808, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- American Sunroof Company and United Automobile Workers Local 985, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Babcock & Wilcox Company Barberton, Ohio, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Budd Company (Clinton Plant) and UAW, Local # 39 Gr. No. 73-7, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Citizens Gas and Coke Utility and Int'l Bro. Elec. Workers Local 1400 Gr. No. 73-06, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Columbus and Southern Ohio Electric and International Bro. Elec. Workers Local 1466, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Cleveland Elec. Illuminating Case No. 5330020870 and Utility Workers Local 270 Gr. No. 90-MD-70, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Cleveland Elec. Illuminating Co. and Utility Workers Local 270 Case# 5330006470, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Besser Company and United Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers Local 472, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Champion International Corp. and UPIU - Local 1967 - Grievance 449-75-3, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- The Carpenter Steel Co. and The United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Chicago Metro. Area Race Track Owners and I.B.E.W. Local 134 - Wage Arbitration, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Conn Organ Corporation and Local 1314 UAW Madison, Indiana Case No. 5230018275, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- CTS of PADUCAH, Inc. and UAW Local 1125 Gr. No. 128, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW Gr.#67-14, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW Gr. 67-57, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW Gr. 67-14, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America Local 1196 #3234, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 2478, USW - Arb. #395 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 2478, USW - Arb. #383 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 2478 USW - Arb. #381 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW - Arb. #373 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 2478, USW - Arb. #378 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 2478, USW - Arb. #368, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 1138, USW (W. Leechburg Works), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Allegheny Ludlum and Local 1138, USW (W. Leechburg Wks), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Allegheny Ludlum(General Dummy File) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW Local 1138 Arb No. 398399400, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and USW Local 1138 Arb. No. 401, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and Local 1138 USW(W. Leechburg Wks), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Allegheny Ludlum and Local 1138 USW (W. Leechburg Wks) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Robbins, Louise Litrich - Papers (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Allegheny Ludlum (W. Leechburg Wks) and Local 1138 USW, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and USW of America Local 1196 Gr. #3244, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and USW Local Union No. 2693 Gr. # 70 778 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and U.S.A. - Local Union No. 2693 Gr. # 70782, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and U.S.A. - Local Union No. 2693, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and U.S.A. - Local Union No. 2693, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and U.S.A - Local Union No. 2693, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and U.S.A., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. Brackenridge Works and United Steelworkers of America Local 1196 Gr. No. 3463, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. Brackenridge Works and United Steelworkers of America Local 1196 Gr. No. 3467 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Current Labor Developments, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America, No. 2693 Gr. No. 74:1020, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America, No. 2693 Gr. No. 73:994, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America, No. 2693, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America, No. 2693 Gr. No. 73:952, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America No. 2693 Gr. No. 73:997, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America No. 2693 Gr. No. 74:1006, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America, No. 2693 Gr. No. 74:1048, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America No. 72:918, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries Inc., and United Steelworkers Local 2242 Gr. No. 72-29, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries, Inc. and United Steelworkers, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corp. and United Steelworkers of America Local 2693, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America Local 2693 Gr No. 72:932, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America Local 2693 Gr. No. 72:915, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Allegheny Ludlum Steel and United Steelworkers of America Local 2693 Gr. No. 71:873, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)